to the outside world. It's really boring, but now we're making about 60k a month.
If you look online right now, literally everyone is chasing the same AI app ideas.
But what if I told you that building in a boring niche is actually where the real money's at?
What started as a side project has since grown into a full-time business?
Well, meet Thomas. He's a guy who spent years in a boring night of five doing the same manual tasks.
Then one day he thought, what if I could automate all this and turn it into a business?
I realized it can sometimes take an hour to successfully package an application.
But when I looked more at the solutions out there, they didn't really fit what I wanted.
So, he built and launched a tiny boring app. And today, that app makes over $60,000 a month.
So I asked Thomas to come onto the channel to break it all down. And in this episode, we'll dive into
how to find boring app ideas that can make money, though one piece of content that got him hundreds
of paying users overnight for free. And how a million dollar idea might be sitting right in front of
your face right now. This one is going to be fun. I'm Pat Walls, and this is Starter Story.
All right guys, real quick before we dive in, Thomas is about to break down how we built this boring
SaaS into a $60,000 per month business. And I think micro SaaS projects like this are super underrated.
So we put together a free report with 52 proven micro SaaS ideas that you can draw inspiration
from. We'll talk a little bit more about that later. But for now, let's get into the video.
Okay, Tom, welcome to the channel. Tell me about who you are, what you built, and what's your story?
Hey, everyone. I'm the founder of Packager. It's a browser-based tool that allows IT admins to
deploy applications to a platform called Microsoft Intune with one click. And now we're making about
60k a month. As you can see here, we did 447k as opposed to 910k, which is really good growth for us,
and we're really happy with that. That's insane. This business is doing $60,000 a month in this sort of
like boring idea I've never even heard of. Let's talk about the idea and how you found this idea.
I think a lot of people watching this are like, hey, where can I find an idea like this? So how did
you come up with the idea for this and how you validated it? As I was working with Intune, I realized
it can sometimes take an hour to successfully package an application and verify that it's going
to install. I started looking on forums and I noticed there were a lot of other IT admins that had
the exact same problem. But when I looked more at the solutions out there, they didn't really fit what
I wanted. They were either too technical, too expensive. So I thought, you know, there's room or
there was a niche to build cost-affordable browser-based modern tool that could do, you know, just one simple
job deploy applications. When I had built this, this was before AI coding tools like cursor and
clawed code existed. A lot of this had to be manually written by myself. I can definitely say it's
great now that some AI tools do exist and makes it a lot easier. Okay, cool. Well, thanks for sharing
that. The more important thing to talk about now is obviously distribution validation. So how did you
find your first customer for this boring SaaS? Yep. And how did you grow up from there? Once we had,
at the time, what we thought was a working MVP. We knew it was time to get it out there and see if
anyone actually was interested in using the product. We knew that Reddit would be the best place to do
this. So we launched the product completely free. It gained a lot of traction quickly and some love
the product. Some gave us really good feedback and there were some people that were just downright
rude and left, you know, pretty harsh comments. And then that's something I've had to really learn
if you want to make it. You sort of have to be able to accept that some people are just not going to
like what you built. After fixing the early bugs and stabilizing the platform based on the initial
feedback, we decided to bring in a $25 US subscription fee per month. That's when we started to make
money from it. I remember sitting there and getting the first notification on my phone of a customer
signed up and was actually willing to pay for something I'd built. It was very exciting. Once we
moved past the initial beta phase, probably the most effective strategy and something I'd recommend
for everyone is partnering with people who specialize in the products. So for us, that was
Microsoft MVPs. They would create demos of the products, which was a highly targeted audience. That
approach was really, really good because I'm really into like planting seeds for marketing. And so like a
YouTube video, for instance, someone could stumble across it two years later and become a customer,
just something that you paid for a long time ago. So that return on investment is huge.
Thomas's story is incredible. $60,000 a month, thousands of paying customers and 100% bootstrapped.
But here's the thing about the type of people that use this product. They really care about security
and compliance. These are the types of customers who want to know whether your product is
sock to compliant or ISO 27001 certified. And if the answer is no, you might be in trouble.
This is why we partnered with Vanta on this video. Vanta automates all the painful parts of
compliance. So you can keep building instead of drowning in paperwork. Right now, Vanta is offering
a special deal for starter story viewers. So if you're building for businesses and want to skip the
compliance headache, then check out Vanta at the first link in the description. Huge thank you to
Vanta for this partnership. All right, let's get back to the episode. You found a great SaaS idea. But
I think a lot of people watching this are wondering, how do I find a low competition niche SaaS that can
make $60,000 a month. So if you were to start over today knowing everything that you know, what would you do?
Step one is to build in an area where you already have credibility. For instance, working in Microsoft
Intune to the outside world. But I was living and breathing Microsoft Intune. I've even had customers
talk to me when I've supported them with something that they can tell that I really love what I'm doing.
So find something that you're credible in. Step two is to look for pain points instead of ideas.
If you're noticing that people where you're working are complaining about something, look to see if there's
a solution there that you can build a product. Customers will ultimately end up buying to help with
that issue. Step three is to avoid competing with the masses. While they fight over the huge markets,
there's an always an opportunity to target the smaller audiences that want something different. And
in our instance, it was the competitors focusing on the customers with millions of devices where we were
targeting the smaller businesses and there was plenty of them and enough for us to make a full-time
business out of it. Step four is to charge early, even if the prices low. We charge during the beta
and I guess that really validated that customers were willing to pay. There's no point chasing that idea
if in the early stages no one's willing to pay for it. It just doesn't make any sense. Step five is
to optimize for freedom instead of scale at all costs. So for us, we've got a really small team.
We focused on running things with small costs. That means that the income that we make is ours.
And we've been able to work from home and we've been able to have work life balance and I can
truly say that building a business I've been able to build a life that I'm really happy with.
Okay, this is what I love about Thomas' story. He did not build something flashy. He found a boring
overlooked problem and now he makes $60,000 a month from it. So you might be watching and wondering
where do I find a niche like that? And that's exactly why we built the micro-sass ideas database.
It's a free report breaking down 52 micro-sass ideas that are already making millions with
the real revenue numbers, growth tactics and pricing models that actually work. You can dig through
this data right now and find a boring, profitable niche that nobody's paying attention to. So my question
is what are you waiting for? Hit the link in the description, grab the report for free, and start
building your next idea. All right, let's get back to the episode. Thanks for sharing that playbook,
great playbook for trying to find a SaaS in 2026. I really still don't understand this Microsoft
Intune thing. Would you be able to just show me a quick demo of how it works? It's a browser-based
tool that helps IT admins deploy software through Microsoft Intune with one click. We're here in the app
library. We've got our test company package selected. All we need to do is come here and select
add an app. You can either select a custom application, which is something that you've uploaded yourself
or one from our own catalog. So we'll go ahead and do one from the catalog. These are all pre-managed
applications. For instance, we can come here, we can click seven zip, it gets added in, and you can see
here from the status, it's awaiting deployment. So we can come down to click deployment. You get a few
options to change a few settings and do some advanced configurations, and we'll just click
deploy to Intune. And that sends a request to the backend servers, which packages up the app,
and uploads it into their Microsoft tenant. And this brings open Intune, and we can see the
application is here ready to deploy. It brings in metadata like the description, logo, and then
you can view it for a few different details. So all we have to do is come down here, and we can assign
to all devices. And that's it. It'll now deploy out to all the company devices.
Well, I have no idea exactly what you did there, because I don't know anything about Microsoft Intune,
but what I think is cool is that your app does something pretty simple. I don't want to make it feel
smaller than it is, because I'm sure it's complex behind the scenes. But when I look at that,
it doesn't have any fancy design. It does something that's useful to companies to use, and it makes $60,000
a month. I mean, that's amazing. On that same note, I'm curious, what's the tech stack behind this,
how complicated was this to build? The main tech stack behind it is we use BubbleIO, which is on the front
end. We do all the package build and testing using GitHub actions, and we host all our code base there
as well. We use Microsoft Azure for all our serverless functions, and then we use Monday.com.
We use that for tracking development progress and managing tickets. And then on top of that,
we have Microsoft 365 licensing for each of the staff members.
Okay, cool. Well, thanks for sharing that. Last question, then we ask all founders to come on
start a story. If you could go back in time and stand on young Tom's shoulders before you've
built this $60,000 per month SaaS idea, what would be your advice? My advice, and this goes for anyone,
just start with the tools available today, or code and chat GBT. Building software has never been
more accessible, but the downside of that means that someone else could build your idea while you're
still sitting there planning it. So speed is the key, you get things going. You want to launch early and
share it with your target audience, and then listen closely to the feedback that they provide. From
there, it just becomes a continuous cycle of improving the product based on what the customers need
and want. And there comes your continuous improvement and development.
Cool. That's great advice. Thank you, Tom, for coming out of the channel and sharing. You obviously
didn't come here to benefit a whole lot because there's probably not a lot of Microsoft intune
users watching this. So thank you for sharing and showing that it can make $60,000 from a boring SaaS.
Thanks for having me on, guys. All right, producer Gus. What do you think? It just reminds me that
there's a million ways to build a successful business. I spend a lot of time on X. You probably do too.
A lot of people watching this do and like trying to find ideas from like this like social media,
echo chamber, bubble about all these AI app ideas. Like if you want to find an idea that can actually
make money in the long term, like his business, he didn't show these numbers, but I assume it's really
low churn. It's IT admins and people using this stuff inside of companies is extremely low churn.
This is a great business. Anyone watching this should realize that if it's boring and it doesn't make
sense, that might be actually direction to go. Yeah, I can think about all the times I've sat in my
nine or five and thought, man, I wish this was easier. That's kind of what he did.
If you are in a job and you're looking for an idea, you want to build something on this side,
maybe you could do something similar. Even if you don't know how to code, if you want to do that,
you can. If you join Starter Story Build, and if you do, we'll help you find an idea,
help you build it and launch it and get in the hands of real users in just a couple days.
I'll put that link in the description. Thank you guys for watching this one. See you in the next one.