Students book.
Page 28.
4.
Hugo's school bag.
It's a school day today.
Right.
What's in my bag?
My new crayons and paints.
My older razor and phone.
But where is my ruler?
Oh,
there,
with my book.
And where is my pen?
Oh,
there it is.
Good.
Look at the clock.
Bye,
mom.
Sue.
I've got my school bag.
See you.
Run to the bus stop.
Quick.
And jump on the bus.
High grace.
Hello,
Nick.
We love our new playground.
Let's have some fun.
Here,
catch this ball.
And jump and run.
This is my classroom.
And this is Miss Rice.
She's our new teacher.
She's really nice.
We're making a poster.
Right.
What's in my bag?
My new crayons and paints.
My old eraser and phone.
But where is my ruler?
It's not here with my book.
And where is my pen?
It's not here.
Oh,
no.
Look.
Don't worry.
Says Mark.
Here you are.
Have my ruler.
I've got two.
There for you.
It's okay.
Says me.
Here you are.
Have my pen.
I've got three.
For you and me.
Thank you.